JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

MOHAMED ERRAZAK ALLAH

SUMMARY

Passionated junior software developer and entrepreneur with more than 2+ years of field experience. Worked on successful personal projects, looking to get in the professional field. Motivated, punctual, and open-minded, adapts easily to various environments. I can work alone or in a team.

CONTACT

errazakallah.hu@gmail.com

+36 30 464 0203

Oktober 6, Budapest, Hungary

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/errazakallah/

LANGUAGES

Arabic (Native)

English (Fluent)

French (Intermediate)

Hungarian (Beginner)

EXPERIENCE

Founder / Designer

(Start-up) Self-employed Oct 2018 - Mar 2020

Develops, expands and the design of the $2\,eCommerce$ websites (NDZ / MFB)

Identity designs for local businesses: restaurants, coffee.

Software Developer

Self-employed Jul 2017 - Sep 2018

Android games development

Software development, Android Games, Unity Game engine, 3D design, UI/UX design, C#, games & unity & coding solutions, SEO, accessibility.

Software Developer

Self-employed Jun 2016 - Jul 2017

Android Applications development Android studio, Software development, content manager, UI/UX design, Java, Kotlin & coding solutions, SEO, accessibility.

TOP SKILLS

- Software Design & Development
- Front-End development (Semantic HTML, Clean, maintainable CSS)
- JavaScript
- Design
- Soft Skills (Passionate, Fast learner, Strong communications skills, Self-motivated, Team worker, Marketing)

CURRENTLY LEARNING MORE ABOUT

- Web development
- Advanced JavaScript
- React
- UI/UX Design
- Git
- Bootstrap
- Sass

EDUCATION

Bsc, Computer Science Engineering Óbuda University Sep 2020 - Present

About: programming, systems and architecture, software development and testing, web applications and databases, algorithms and data structures, etc...

language of studies: English

WEB MKTG

Graduate School Of Technology, Oujda (ESTO)

Sep 2018 - Jun 2020

Web design and marketing, Branding, Web marketing strategies, Content Marketing, Mobile Marketing, SEO and Digital Campaigns, etc...

language of studies: French

Physics science Omar Ibn Abdel Aziz Sep 2015 - Jun 2018

About:

Diploma: Baccalaureat
Field: Physics science
Main publicate: Math. Physics

Main subjects: Math, Physics language of studies: Arabic